[theme music playing]
[Diego] Who are you, Ivy Aguas?
You never told me anything
about your family.
It's like you don't want
anyone entering your world.
[Tonio] I only killed the victims.
But I'm not the one who buried them.
-Who did?
-[Tonio] It's Noel.
Who ordered you to do it?
It was Raul. Raul Torillo.
[Ivy] Raul, you monster!
You wretched bastard!
Get ready, Raul, because
I'm going to take my mom back.
[Raul] I'm already packing our things.
We're going to move somewhere else.
[Julio] Who told you
to take over everything I left behind?
You have no right sitting
-in my goddamn chair!
-[glass shatters]
[Arnaldo] Our beloved congressman,
Señor Julio Ardiente, will return!
[Emilia] I'll treat him like
one of my enemies.
You're going to have Julio killed?
Poblacion Ardiente is too small
for the both of us.
[Ivy] How did Lily
and her family disappear?
All I remember is her parents
had a fight with my dad.
I guess they left because
they didn't want any trouble.
It's like she's keeping something from me.
What do you think it is?
I don't know,
but I want to know her more
because I love her, Nanny.
What?!
[Ivy] It's your son's birthday.
-Yeah, I know.
-[Ivy] So, let's have fun?
Hello?
Hello? Are you with Camia Cruz?
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
[somber music playing]
Jasmin? What are you doing?
Don't touch that. Come here.
You better rest in your room now.
[emotional music playing]
Go on.
Hurry up.
Ivy?
Is everything all right?
Why is my husband's phone with you?
[tense music playing]
Oh, you're right!
I thought it was mine, Emilia.
I was talking to Mr. Torillo earlier.
Tell him not to leave
his phone lying around
because someone might take it from him.
Thanks for the advice, Ivy.
We really should cut off the hands of…
cell phone thieves.
[Emilia clears throat]
So, did--
So, you're waiting for someone.
No. I just asked the waiter
to bring me a drink.
Here's your phone.
Where did you get this?
From Miss Aguas.
You know what? I was wondering
why Miss Aguas had your phone.
Any thoughts?
I don't know either, Emilia.
You lying bastard.
[tense music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention, please?
I'd like to propose a toast for Arnaldo.
Mayor Arnaldo,
can you please join me here?
Sure. Excuse me.
How about a big hand
for my son, Mayor Arnaldo?
-[applause]
-Thank you. Thank you.
Arnaldo, happy, happy birthday.
I wish you all the best
and may you continue to shine
for the people of Ardiente.
Happy birthday, son. I love you.
Thank you very much.
-Cheers!
-[guests] Cheers!
-[glasses clink]
-[woman] Happy birthday, Mayor!
[Emilia] Happy birthday, Mayor.
-[Arnaldo] Thank you!
-[Emilia] A round of applause
for Mayor Arnaldo.
[applause]
[Arnaldo] Thank you, Mom.
Thank you very much
for coming to my party.
But for now, I'd like to request everyone
to turn your attention to the big screen.
There's an important person
who wants to join our party.
-[suspenseful sting]
-Happy, happy birthday,
my favorite grandson.
[suspenseful music playing]
Thank you very much, Grandpa!
How are you there in the States?
I'm good. And you should
stop worrying about me.
Nothing can kill me here
in America, aside from my heart.
[laughs]
That's a bad joke, Grandpa.
I just want to make sure
that everything is all right.
Remember, Arnaldo.
No one can bring me down.
And once I return to Poblacion Ardiente…
I will clean up all the trash
that gathered there while I was away.
[dramatic music playing]
You know who you are,
and I'll be seeing you soon.
Ladies and gentlemen, that's
Congressman Julio Ardiente!
[applause]
[Arnaldo] Okay. Well,
let's go back to the party.
Thank you very much!
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy? Ivy! Ivy! Ivy, wait.
Diego.
I just want to apologize
for what I did earlier.
It's fine. I understand.
Sorry, I have to go.
Wait.
I just want to explain
why I did all that earlier.
Diego, it's fine.
You don't have to explain.
Ivy, you have to listen to me.
Please, Diego. I don't have time for this.
We can talk some other time.
Sorry, I have to go.
Ivy…
[somber guitar music playing]
No matter how long it takes,
I'll wait for you, Ivy.
Because I love you.
[unsettling music playing]
[Ivy] Hello, are you with Camia Cruz?
[echoing] Camia Cruz.
Camia Cruz. Camia Cruz.
Atty. Dante Cruz.
This is my daughter, Lily.
And my wife, Camia.
[unsettling music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[engine starts]
[dark piano music playing]
[sobbing]
-[screams]
-[glass shatters]
[breathing heavily]
Emilia!
Auntie, Papa is alive and well.
I don't understand!
Why can't he just die?!
Weeds are hard to get rid of, Emilia.
[exhales sharply, sniffles]
But, Auntie, I don't understand.
[sniffles]
He will regret coming back here
to Poblacion Ardiente.
I will make his life a living hell.
[dramatic music playing]
[Belen] Jasmin! Your food is ready!
I'm coming in, okay?
Asleep again?
I'll just leave your food here.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Belen] Just eat when you feel like it.
-[glass shatters]
-[screams in pain]
[Belen whimpering]
[Belen] Jasmin! Jasmin! Jasmin!
Jasmin! Jasmin!
Jasmin!
[suspenseful music playing]
[pants, screams]
[screams]
[car horn honking]
[suspenseful music playing]
[panting]
-[horn honking]
-[yelps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[tires screech]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
Mom?
[somber music playing]
Mom?!
Mom!
-[Raul] Auntie? Auntie.
-[Belen crying] Raul.
-Auntie.
-Raul.
-What happened to you?
-Jasmin got away.
-What?!
-Jasmin ran away!
-Where is Jasmin?!
-Look for her! Find her.
[gloomy music playing]
Mom! Mom, where are you? Mom!
Mom, don't be scared.
Mom, I'm your daughter!
Mom!
[pensive music playing]
[young Lily] Mom?
[Camia] Go on. Hurry. Get out of here.
Mom! Mom, wait! Mom! Mom!
[line ringing]
[tense music playing]
Madrigal, where have you been?
I haven't seen you around.
I was in the area, Mayor.
I was just outside.
Have you seen Miss Aguas?
I've been looking for her.
She's not answering her phone.
I haven't seen her, Mayor.
[exhales sharply] Where is she?
[tense music playing]
Look for Miss Aguas. Now. Go!
Mom! Mom, wait! Mom, wait!
Mom, it's me, Lily!
[panting]
Mom, it's me, your daughter, Lily.
Wait! Don't leave.
Mom…
Mom! Mom!
[tires screech]
Mom!
[screams]
My mom… That was my mom.
[instrumental theme music playing]
My mom is alive.
[exhales]
But why did she run?
[panting]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[Camia exclaims, cries]
-[shushes]
Arnaldo, where is your father?
Now Dad's gone missing, too.
What?! Why? Who else is missing?
Mayor, some of our men
saw Miss Aguas leave
right after Sir Raul.
They left together?
Where did they go?
Outside Poblacion Ardiente.
[tense music playing]
-[screaming]
-[Belen] Raul!
-Aunt Belen.
-[screaming continues]
Aunt Belen, get the door ready! The key!
[screaming, sobbing]
[screams]
-[screaming]
-[door slams]
[screams]
[Camia pounding on door]
[sobbing]
[sighs] I guess…
it would be best if we go away for now.
We're moving away from here.
It's late. You can just go tomorrow.
No. We have to leave now.
A lot of people are on to me.
I can't risk it. I have to hide Camia.
-[tense music playing]
-Camia? Who is Camia?
[suspenseful sting]
Raul, tell me the truth.
Who is that woman?
[tense music playing]
Ivy?
[suspenseful music playing]
Raul, I've been suspicious for a while.
I didn't say anything because I trust you.
Who is that woman?
Why are you locking her up?!
Auntie, stay out of this. Okay?
Don't worry. We won't trouble you anymore.
And you won't see us again.
Just don't say anything to anyone.
-But, Raul--
-No, Auntie.
You don't understand.
You don't know anything.
[foreboding music playing]
Auntie, what are you doing?! Huh?!
-What?!
-Raul!
-What are you doing?!
-I can't let you do this!
You don't understand!
You don't understand! Give me the key!
-Please stop, Raul.
-Give me the key!
-[punches]
-[groans]
[Raul] Come on, Auntie!
[groaning, crying]
Raul. Raul, Raul…
[suspenseful music playing]
[lock disengages]
Camia…
Camia, I won't hurt you. Don't be afraid.
I just want you to know
that nobody can keep us apart.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[Camia screaming]
[muffled screaming]
[Raul shushes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
[panting]
[Diego] Ivy.
Ivy, what happened to you?
Where have you been?
My mom…
What? Ivy.
Ivy, Prianka's been dead for years.
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy?
[engine starts]
Emilia. We can't contact Raul.
And it turns out,
Ivy has gone missing with him.
Coincidence?
In the world of traitors,
there is no such thing.
I've been married to Raul for many years.
And I know when my husband
is up to something.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
[Jepoy] Ivy.
Ivy, you left all of a sudden.
The mayor and the governor
have been looking for you.
Where did you go?
I followed Raul.
Jepoy…
[instrumental theme music playing]
I saw my mom.
I'm sure it was her.
But she ran from me.
I kept calling for her, but…
I don't understand.
I couldn't catch up to her, Jepoy.
But I'm sure that was my mom.
Ivy, listen to me.
Don't ever blame yourself
for what happened.
What's important is that
we're sure your mom is alive.
I know what to do…
now that I've confirmed Raul has her.
But I have to be careful, Jepoy…
now that I know my mom is still alive.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Mom…
[sniffles]
Why, Mom?
Why…
Why doesn't my mother remember me?
We've been waiting for you, Diego.
[giggles]
Nanny, why did you wait for me?
[Pandoy] Well, she's just been
so giddy over you and Ms. Aguas.
-[laughing]
-Hey! It's not like that!
It's really not like that!
I'm just happy. So, Diego?
Have you confessed your feelings to her?
Does our little Diego
finally have a girlfriend?
No. That didn't happen.
Nanny, after we talked,
she left right away.
On my way home,
I saw her looking like a mess.
She looked like she just cried.
-What?
-And she said…
she saw her mother.
What? Who? Prianka?
I thought she's been dead for years.
Is she being haunted?
Hey! Don't say that.
Maybe she just missed her,
so she imagined things.
I'm confused if she's referring
to Prianka Aguas or Camia Cruz.
Nanny, I have a hunch that Ivy
and Lily are the same person.
Then, what do you plan to do now, Diego?
Are you going to investigate Miss Aguas?
Are you still going to court her?
[somber piano music playing]
-[sighs]
-[Loring] Diego…
maybe you're falling in love with Miss Ivy
because you think that she's Lily.
What if that's not true?
Would you still be in love with Miss Ivy?
Nanny, where's Raul?
He's not here yet, Governor.
But you have a visitor.
Emilia.
-Hi.
-Ivy!
I just wanted to ask
how your charity event went.
-Well?
-Oh.
It was a success.
The poor were so happy with my gifts.
You're so used to acting
like you care for the poor.
Of course. It's all for show, Ivy.
It's all for publicity.
Good point. But, don't
the press people ask you
why you're not with your husband
most of the time?
Of course they don't.
The people are used to seeing Raul
popping up and disappearing.
But in the end…
he still comes home to me.
Okay. So, where's Raul?
You know…
I was about to ask you the same question.
A lot of people noticed
that you and Raul left the party
at the same time.
Like you just vanished into thin air.
You know, Ivy, what I hate
the most are traitors.
Are you trying to say something, Emilia?
No, I'm not. How about you?
Are you trying to say something?
I don't like women flirting
with my husband.
Are you flirting with Raul?
Flirting? You call that flirting?
Did it ever occur to you that maybe,
I was only being friendly
with your husband?
Emilia, please don't make
your insecurities too obvious.
[scoffs]
Ivy, I'm not playing games here.
Don't even think about betraying me
because you won't like
having me as an enemy.
I'm not playing games, either, Emilia.
And I am not the type of woman
who likes having affairs
because I don't intend
on tainting my reputation
just to sleep with your
good-for-nothing husband.
And I won't pour money into your family
just because of a man like your husband.
Do you want me to pull out
all my investments?
Do you think your father would like that?
Don't forget, Emilia,
Julio is all set to return.
Keep that in mind.
Project your insecurities
elsewhere, but not onto me.
[tense music playing]
I will find you, Raul,
no matter where you hide.
[unsettling music playing]
[suspenseful sting]
[suspenseful music playing]
Hello? Anyone home?
[Belen] How may I help you?
I'm looking for someone.
Her name is Camia Cruz.
Who are you?
I am Ivy Aguas.
Camia Cruz is in our list
of missing persons,
and the authorities are looking for her.
Did you know that?
I don't know anything.
Hold on, ma'am.
It's obvious that you're lying.
I can see it in your eyes.
Wait. Did someone hurt you?
What happened to that?
It's none of your business!
Let's just say…
I can protect you
from whoever you're protecting
by not telling me where Camia Cruz is.
You have my word.
But if you don't tell me
where Camia Cruz is,
mark my words, you will rot in prison.
[suspenseful music playing]
[voice breaking]
He told me her name was Jasmin.
But believe me, I didn't know
he was planning something bad!
Raul left with Camia last night
and went somewhere far away.
Raul… Raul Torillo?
He has Camia.
[suspenseful music playing]
Raul, you bastard.
[tense music playing]
[tense music intensifies]
[mysterious unsettling music playing]
[suspenseful sting]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
Papa?
Emilia.
Emilia!
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[tapping sound]
[carpenter] Oh. Good morning, Governor.
Hey! What's so good
about the morning?! Huh?!
You're already causing
a disturbance this early!
-Get out of my sight!
-Yes, ma'am.
Get out!
[ominous music playing]
Emilia.
Is everything okay?
Yes, Auntie. I'm okay.
[woman] Congressman
Julio Ardiente has arrived.
[supporters shouting indistinctly]
[supporter 1] Señor Julio is here!
[supporters whooping]
[suspenseful music playing]
[supporter 2] Congressman!
[supporter 3] Welcome back, Congressman!
We missed you, Congressman!
[supporter 1] Welcome back, Señor Julio!
[supporters] Welcome back!
[supporters chanting]
Señor Julio! Señor Julio!
Señor Julio!
[Arnaldo] Welcome back, Grandpa.
[Julio] Thank you, grandson.
Thank you very much to the
people of Poblacion Ardiente,
and most especially,
to all of you, my children.
Thank you very much for your prayers.
I wouldn't have gotten better
without them.
Thank you, everyone.
And now, I have returned, fully recovered,
and even stronger than an ox.
-[laughter]
-Long live Señor Julio!
I'm eager to assume my duties
and serve you.
Of course, we'll clean up
whatever needs to be cleaned.
And if needed, we'll cut off
the horns of those devils
who played king here during my absence.
[suspenseful music playing]
Viva Ardiente!
[supporters] Viva Ardiente!
[supporter] Viva Ardiente!
[suspenseful music playing]
Emilia. Emilia.
I missed you!
Aren't you going to give
your father a hug?
-Hi, Papa.
-Come here.
I missed you, Papa. I missed you.
I missed you, too, Emilia.
[chuckling]
I missed you. Welcome back.
-[sniffles]
-[laughing]
You can't fool me
with your crocodile tears,
hugs, and kisses.
I know what you've been doing
while I was gone.
[both faking laughter]
[Emilia] Papa…
Again, thank you all.
Thank you for welcoming me
and for your prayers.
Thank you very much!
[supporter] Long live Señor Julio!
[in unison] Long live Señor Julio!
[supporters chanting]
Señor Julio! Señor Julio!
Viva Ardiente!
[in unison] Viva Ardiente!
[supporters] Viva Ardiente!
[chuckles]
[gloomy music playing]
[gasps]
[shushes] Jasmin.
Jasmin? Jasmin, wait. Listen to me.
Nobody's after you anymore, okay?
You don't need to run,
you don't need to hide.
I'm right here, okay?
As your husband, I will take care of you.
I won't let anybody take you from me.
Okay?
We'll be okay here.
We'll be happy here, Jasmin.
That's enough. Don't worry.
You're safe with me.
[tense music playing]
You might be hungry.
I'll make you something to eat.
Okay? Stay here and rest.
Just rest.
No. This is not happening.
This is not happening.
[cries] This is not happening.
[unsettling music playing]
[flicks lighter]
This can't be happening.
Emilia?
Auntie, this is not happening, right?
This can't be happening!
Calm down, Emilia.
Auntie, he cannot take
everything away from me!
He cannot do this to me, Auntie!
-Calm down, Emilia!
-No, Auntie!
-Calm down!
-[yelps]
If there's one thing
I know about predators, Emilia,
it's that they smell fear!
You can't allow Julio to smell your fear!
That was the downfall of your mother,
and I'll be damned
if I let that happen to you.
He may be Julio Ardiente,
but he's only just a man!
Do you understand me, Emilia?
Do you understand me?!
It's time to find out if that
woman is with us or against us.
You know very well what happens
to our family's enemies, right?
[Emilia] Raul, I'm sure Papa
will have you killed.
You better stay at your parents' place
in San Ildefonso.
[Ivy] San Ildefonso.
That's where Raul
could be hiding my mother.
Is there a problem, Diego?
[Diego] I won't let anything
happen to you.
I will protect you from my family.
[theme music playing]